module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is Kendrick Lamar\'s last name?', 
    a: 'Lamar',
    b: 'Kendrick',
    c: 'Duckworth',
    d: 'Knowles',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is O\'Shea Jackson\'s rap alias?', 
    a: 'Ice T',
    b: 'Ice Cube',
    c: 'Vanilla Ice',
    d: 'Billy the Wizard',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which hip hop artist was born in Austin?', 
    a: 'Missy Elliott',
    b: 'Ciara',
    c: 'Lil Kim',
    d: 'Nicki Minaj',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is NOT one of 50 Cent\'s albums?', 
    a: 'Get Rich or Die Trying',
    b: 'Massacre',
    c: 'Beg For Mercy',
    d: 'Chicken and Beer',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'How old is Pharrell?', 
    a: '34',
    b: '37',
    c: '42',
    d: '46',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was Wreckx-n-Effect\'s most popular single in 1992?', 
    a: 'Here We Come',
    b: 'Tell Me How You Feel',
    c: 'Rump Shaker',
    d: 'My Cutie',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does N.E.R.D. stand for?', 
    a: 'No-one Ever Really Dies',
    b: 'Never Ever Run Distances',
    c: 'No Early Rising Dude',
    d: 'Nancy Expresses Real Disdain',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the title of Tyler, The Creator\'s latest album?', 
    a: 'EARFQUAKE',
    b: 'Flower Boy',
    c: 'IGOR',
    d: 'Cherry Bomb',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is better known as Lil Wayne?', 
    a: 'Wayne Michael Carter Jr',
    b: 'Michael Wayne Carter Jr',
    c: 'Michael Dwayne Carter Jr',
    d: 'Dwayne Michael Carter Jr',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where was Kid Cudi born?', 
    a: 'Houston TX',
    b: 'Cleveland OH',
    c: 'Brooklyn NY',
    d: 'Atlanta GA',
    answer: 'b'
  }
];